javeu.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy Policy - JavEU - JAV Free Streamming Openload and Videomega

**This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on javeu.com**

The security of your Data is very important to javeu.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults with an age of 18 years and over or having attained the age of majority in their state/land. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

**By using of the website javeu.com you agree to the following provisions of this privacy policy.**

### Data collected

**Personal Information:**

Users which are non-Registered can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However the visitor’s IP address will be recorded, if there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.

Cookies: When you visit javeu.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. Fuukk.com uses cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site’s features may not function properly.

Log File Information: When you visit javeu.com, our servers may automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

### Uses of Information

If you contact us via email, your email address is displayed to the javeu.com private mail, etc.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).

We analyse aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the javeu.com user-experience.

### Disclosure of Information

If under duty to do so javeu.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms and Conditions; or to protect the rights, property or safety of javeu.com or our subscribers. This includes exchanging information with governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms and Conditions. It is javeu.com’s policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address), third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent.

### Security

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password, which enables you to access certain parts of our Site or third parties, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure, but Fuukk.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to javeu.com and you do so at your own risk.

### Your Rights

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the ?contact us section? or via e-mail: contact@javeu.com.
